GRAYSON CONNOR



(903) 421-6187



graysonrayconnor@gmail.com



6001 Shepherd Mountain Cv. Austin, TX 78730



http://www.linkedin.com/in/grayson-co

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Analytical Web Developer with 6+ years of experience in **issue identification** and resolution. Strong background in **web development** and data analysis by utilizing programming technologies including APIs, JavaScript, and others. Adept at **ensuring regulatory compliance**. Competent in **using various software** for recognizing and resolving application and device failures.

EDUCATION

Web Developer Program Participant, Bloc.io, Austin, TX Aug 2017 – Jul 2018

> Obtained knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 3, Bootstrap 4, JavaScript, jQuery, and React.

Developed personal skills in the fields of media marketing, UX/UI design, and customer relationship management.

Implemented various projects, including BlocJams through the utilization of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery.

Boosted acquired knowledge by participating in weekly meetings with mentors and industry professionals oriented to improve participant's professional and technical skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MECHANICAL TECHNICIAN II/SITE SAFETY LEAD, JUMP (Uber),

Austin, TX | Oct 2018 - Apr 2020

Priority on overseeing maintenance of 500 JUMP vehicles and ensuring an OSHA and EHS compliant environment as the Site Safety Lead.

- Guaranteed vehicle safety by developing standard operating procedures and overseeing maintenance for 500 vehicles, including JUMP e-bikes and scooters.
- Identified and resolved device issues through analysis of I.O.T. device states and issue development patterns.
- Ensured safety protocols compliance by providing staff with P.P.E., fire, and biohazard safety equipment, creating protocol documentation, and developing and implementing safety tests.

BACKROOM/LOGISTICS ASSOCIATE, Target,

Sherman, TX | Jun 2015 - Jun 2017

Emphasis on merchandise presentation and communication with customers and the management regarding customer inquiries' resolution.

- Generated company revenue and customer turnaround through the merchandise preparation and presentation and managed 5 inbound and outbound shipments per week on average.
- Provided customer service by assisting 25+ customers daily with their purchase and inquiry resolution.
- Resolved issues regarding inventory inquiries through collaboration with the store management and Target officials.
- Promoted work safety and quality standards by maintaining the backroom in compliance with sanitation standards.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

React

SCSS/SASS

CSS Grid

Flexbox

Bootstrap

Wordpress

VS Code

Git

Netlify

Figma

Canva

SKILLS.

Data Analysis
Standards Implementation
Customer Service
Code Versioning
Written & Verbal Communication
Conflict Resolution
Strategy Development
Issue Identification & Resolution
Business Management

• Ensured work quality and safety by training 10 staff members on inventory management, safety protocols, and equipment usage.

OWNER/MANAGER, Blossom & Bud's,

Sherman, TX | Jul 2013 - Aug 2014

Accent on ensuring customer satisfaction through business management, regulatory compliance, and issue resolution.

- Provided customer service by selling store products such as Japanese shaved ice dessert, Kakigori, and Boba Tea.
- Ensured regulatory compliance through equipment and store maintenance in adherence to sanitation standards.
- Developed strategy plans through performance evaluation, trend identification, and accepting a recommendation from staff/customers.
- Improved work efficiency by assisting in the development and adjustments of menus and budget management.